



1111 Army Navy DR. Apt. 132 Arlington, VA 22202



314-583-3742



wiegand.alex@gmail.com



alex-wiegand.netlify.app

OBJECTIVE

A veteran of the food & beverage industry for over 14 years, I have experience working as part of a team in a fast paced, ever-changing environment. I also have practical experience in designing, developing, and launching a product. I am seeking to leverage this experience to enter the tech industry.



EXPERIENCE

Starbucks

Shift Supervisor • June 2021 - Present • Arlington, VA

Bambara Kitchen & Bar

Lead Bartender • February 2018 − February 2021 • Cambridge, MA

Saloon

Bartender • March 2017 – February 2018 • Sommerville, MA

Over my career in the food service industry, I have learned many soft skills that are useful in any workplace. I have also developed an exceptional work ethic. In addition, I have developed and subsequently trained staff on several cocktail menus.

EDUCATION

Berklee College of Music, Boston, MA

January 2012 - January 2013

SKILLS

Proficient in all major operating systems

| HTML5 | JavaScript | CSS3 |
|--------|------------|---------|
| React | Svelte | Webpack |
| NodeJS | SQL | Express |

MY CERTIFICATES

- CodeCademy
- The Modern JavaScript Bootcamp Andrew Mead Udemy
- Learn JavaScript Online- Jad Joubran

OTHER ACCOMPLISHMENTS

- ❖ Judges Choice Tito's Mary Madness 2019
- Featured in Imbibe magazine October 2019

REFERENCES

Available on request.